<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>uganda on Cork OpenCoffee</title>
    <link>https://localhost/tags/uganda/</link>
    <description>Recent content in uganda on Cork OpenCoffee</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2008 12:03:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://localhost/tags/uganda/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Latest Cork OCC Updates</title>
      <link>https://localhost/2008/07/11/latest-cork-occ-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2008 12:03:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://localhost/2008/07/11/latest-cork-occ-updates/</guid>
      <description>Just a few notes on the latest from Cork OpenCoffee.
 * We&#39;re in today&#39;s Examiner! Half page piece including a picture I took at the Tapasol Demo in the Rubicon Boardroom. * Aileen Cussen wants to thank everyone who donated last Friday. She raised almost €700 from a total of €4000. In addition, she got multiple offers of help and expertise for the trip to Uganda including Wifi/internet guidance, laptop configuration, CD burning and local contacts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Special one-off OpenCoffee in Rubicon this Friday</title>
      <link>https://localhost/2008/06/29/special-one-off-opencoffee-in-rubicon-this-friday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2008 18:26:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://localhost/2008/06/29/special-one-off-opencoffee-in-rubicon-this-friday/</guid>
      <description>The next OCC would normally not be in the Rubicon but we&amp;rsquo;ve decided to have a special joint-one there this coming Friday, July 4th at 10am.
Aileen Cussen, who is an EI D.A. to many of you I&amp;rsquo;m sure (including ourselves) is going to Uganda to help build a school and educate some of the local children for a period of several weeks. It is being done as part of the Lake Lyantonde project which was initiated by the Kabata Farmers Group and run by the local community with an aim of creating awareness of, environmental conservation practices, safe water and sanitation, sustainable agriculture, HIV/Aids, and fostering general development for the community living near Lake Lyantonde.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
