<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>corkopencoffee on Cork OpenCoffee</title>
    <link>/tags/corkopencoffee/</link>
    <description>Recent content in corkopencoffee on Cork OpenCoffee</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2009 08:16:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/corkopencoffee/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Citylocal Cork Sponsoring Cork OpenCoffee</title>
      <link>/2009/09/20/citylocal-cork-sponsoring-cork-opencoffee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2009 08:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2009/09/20/citylocal-cork-sponsoring-cork-opencoffee/</guid>
      <description>Since Cork OpenCoffee began in early 2007, we&amp;rsquo;ve had some intermittent sponsorship of the coffee and scones which has always been appreciated. So we&amp;rsquo;re delighted that Paul Brugger from Citylocal Cork has agreed to sponsor three of the Rubicon sessions (with the first one just two days ago).

This means no more icky instant coffee and the arrival of the great Mr Cotton coffee instead. By the way, well done to Declan for his appearance on TV3 this week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenCoffee Mallow Announced</title>
      <link>/2009/06/25/opencoffee-mallow-announced/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2009 15:42:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2009/06/25/opencoffee-mallow-announced/</guid>
      <description>Elaine Rogers has just announced OpenCoffee Mallow. It&amp;rsquo;s fantastic to see another OCC in Munster and, having talked to Elaine, I know she has a great vision for facilitating business networking in that part of the county.
If you find the trip into Cork City or Limerick too far or you just need a change of scene, then why not attend?
The first one is on in Springfort Hall, New Twopothouse, Mallow, on Tues 7th July 2009 in the main bar from 10 am to 12 pm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dates and some locations for upcoming Cork OpenCoffees</title>
      <link>/2009/06/08/dates-and-some-locations-for-upcoming-cork-opencoffees/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2009 09:04:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2009/06/08/dates-and-some-locations-for-upcoming-cork-opencoffees/</guid>
      <description>We have the following dates and locations finalised for the next few months. For the undecided locations, it will either be Nosh+Coffee in the City Centre or somewhere that we have been invited to. Feel free to invite us somewhere!
We meet, as always, from 10am-12
 * This Friday 12th June - Regus offices in Cork City Gate, Bld 1000, City Gate, Mahon. Suzanne in Regus is kindly hosting OCC and will give anyone who wants a tour of their new facility.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This week&#39;s OpenCoffee in The Rubicon in CIT</title>
      <link>/2009/04/01/this-weeks-opencoffee-in-the-rubicon-in-cit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2009 21:52:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2009/04/01/this-weeks-opencoffee-in-the-rubicon-in-cit/</guid>
      <description>This week&amp;rsquo;s Cork OpenCoffee is in the Rubicon building in CIT from 10am-12pm.
The demo/talk slot is about a new business idea from John Peavoy, Bartosz Ptaszynski and Phoebe Bright. It is about helping companies jumpstart their software ideas. They would like to share their plans so far and hear your views on whether the business will work, and if so, what markets they could target and who they should involve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Blog Header</title>
      <link>/2009/01/25/new-blog-header/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2009 09:46:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2009/01/25/new-blog-header/</guid>
      <description>We have a lovely new custom Cork OpenCoffee blog header courtesy of Brian Clayton. Thanks Brian and thanks to Joe Scanlon for organising!
Now to fix the headers in the sub-pages. Anyone, anyone?
UPDATE: Big thanks to Ann Donnelly for sorting out the header for us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Videos from OCC Today</title>
      <link>/2009/01/09/videos-from-occ-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2009 13:44:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2009/01/09/videos-from-occ-today/</guid>
      <description>Ciara from FindaConferenceVenue got some amazing feedback from the OCC crew today. Whilst I used an external mic, I&amp;rsquo;m not sure it was any better than the built-in one for volume.
Part 1:

Part 2:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Demo tomorrow at OCC is FindaConferenceVenue.com</title>
      <link>/2009/01/08/demo-tomorrow-at-occ-is-findaconferencevenuecom/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2009 18:16:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2009/01/08/demo-tomorrow-at-occ-is-findaconferencevenuecom/</guid>
      <description>Ciara Feely is an expert on venues in Ireland, she established FindaConferenceVenue.com in 2007 and launched this as a venue-finding website. It is the largest and most detailed database of venues in Ireland with over 500 listed.
Ciara would like to do a short demo in order to gain feedback on the site. She is about to introduce changes to the site and would like to get an idea of usability of these.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First set of dates for Cork OCC in 2009</title>
      <link>/2009/01/05/first-set-of-dates-for-cork-occ-in-2009/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2009 21:29:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2009/01/05/first-set-of-dates-for-cork-occ-in-2009/</guid>
      <description>Our first OpenCoffee is Friday 9th in the Rubicon Centre in CIT, this gives us the following dates for the next few months. I&amp;rsquo;ll put these on Upcoming.org too so you can add them to your calendar and auto-monitor for changes.
If you&amp;rsquo;d like to host any of the TBD locations or even replace any Luigi one, just let us know on corkopencoffee AT gmail DOT com
 * 09/01: Location = Rubicon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Open Coffee of 2009 in Cork</title>
      <link>/2009/01/05/first-open-coffee-of-2009-in-cork/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2009 19:02:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2009/01/05/first-open-coffee-of-2009-in-cork/</guid>
      <description>Happy New Year to all, hope you are refreshed, revived and full of vigor and enthusiasm for what 2009 has to offer all of us flegling businesses in the Cork area!
The first OCC of 2009 is on this Friday, the 9th January in the Rubicon Centre in CIT at our usual time of 10am-12pm.
We want to have a brainstorming session for ideas for improvements for the group itself or ideas of events/additions that we can implement in 2009.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cork OpenCoffee in 2009</title>
      <link>/2008/12/31/cork-opencoffee-in-2009/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2008 17:52:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/12/31/cork-opencoffee-in-2009/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve just had a fantastic 2008 in OCC and I think we can make it even better in 2009. A few quick thoughts as we race towards the end of the year.
 OCC only works because of the attendees. Thanks to everyone who even attended one session this year. Ciara and Gordon are doing a fantastic job re-invigorating OCC. I should have asked for their help earlier! I&amp;rsquo;ll post at least three months of dates for 2009 shortly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OCC on 19th?</title>
      <link>/2008/12/13/occ-on-19th/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2008 09:33:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/12/13/occ-on-19th/</guid>
      <description>Gordon is proposing an OCC on the 19th. Vote in the poll if your are interested.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spreading the load</title>
      <link>/2008/11/05/spreading-the-load/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2008 13:53:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/11/05/spreading-the-load/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;d very happy to announce that the organisation of each Cork OpenCoffee session will be split between me, Gordon Murray and Ciara Crossan from now on. I really appreciate them both agreeing to help out and each of us will organise every third event.
You&amp;rsquo;ll see no major difference in OCC except that the person deciding the demos, doing the intros and sending the reminder emails will rotate.
To kick if off, Gordon will be arranging this Friday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nomos Software at OpenCoffee</title>
      <link>/2008/10/26/nomos-software-at-opencoffee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2008 13:06:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/10/26/nomos-software-at-opencoffee/</guid>
      <description>Tricia and David from Nomos Software demoed their software on Friday. Whilst it was a highly technical topic, we had an excellent QA session about the business side of things. From their own site: &amp;ldquo;Nomos Software applies model driven engineering, code generation and declarative rules-based techniques to the management and control of data&amp;rdquo;.

This was the first OCC session where we aimed for tight time control and it worked very well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Few Small Changes to Cork OCC</title>
      <link>/2008/10/15/a-few-small-changes-to-cork-occ/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2008 15:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/10/15/a-few-small-changes-to-cork-occ/</guid>
      <description>Based on feedback from attendees we&amp;rsquo;re making two small changes to the way we do things at OpenCoffee. The first concerns the round-table introductions which many feel are taking up far too much time. So from Oct 24th onwards you have 30 seconds or less to introduce yourself. I recommend three sentences: [1] Your name and your company name [2] What you do (one sentence!) [3] Your current challenge in your business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cork OCC&#39;s Monday talk and next two events</title>
      <link>/2008/10/15/cork-occs-monday-talk-and-next-two-events/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2008 15:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/10/15/cork-occs-monday-talk-and-next-two-events/</guid>
      <description>Monday&amp;rsquo;s special OCC in the NSC was exactly that, special. The boardroom was jammed full of people, many of them new faces to hear Tom Keane talk about Nitrosell, his history and his advice on growing a business. I was completely riveted by what he had to say since so much of it applied directly to what we are doing in LouderVoice. The questions at the end told me that he had affected many of the attendees in the same way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Special OpenCoffee on Monday 13th (Not Friday!)</title>
      <link>/2008/10/07/special-opencoffee-on-monday-13th-not-friday/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2008 13:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/10/07/special-opencoffee-on-monday-13th-not-friday/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re running a special one-off OpenCoffee this coming Monday (13th) instead of the usual Friday. It&amp;rsquo;s a bit unusual in that we&amp;rsquo;ve invited a speaker to come in and talk about how he grew his business and raised funding. That person is Tom Keane, President of Nitrosell. He has a long history in the software biz and I know I&amp;rsquo;m not the only one who has a ton of questions to ask him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A fun Friday in Luigi&#39;s</title>
      <link>/2008/09/14/a-fun-friday-in-luigis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2008 13:35:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/09/14/a-fun-friday-in-luigis/</guid>
      <description>Friday&amp;rsquo;s OpenCoffee was a very lighthearted occasion with 15+ attendees and plenty of technology being passed around. I was pleased to see some new faces too.
A few badly taken pictures:




A video of all the tiny laptops and PDAs that were on display:

The next session is in the Rubicon in CIT on Sep 26th from 10-12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This week&#39;s Cork OCC in Luigi Malones</title>
      <link>/2008/09/10/this-weeks-cork-occ-in-luigi-malones/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2008 09:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/09/10/this-weeks-cork-occ-in-luigi-malones/</guid>
      <description>This week&amp;rsquo;s Cork OpenCoffee is back to our old haunt of Luigi Malones from 10-12 on Friday.
As always with Luigi&amp;rsquo;s, we have no formal demos. However we may have Diarmuid Wrenne and Gordon Murray doing a head2head between their Medion and Asus teeny-tiny laptops. Hopefully we&amp;rsquo;ll broadcast that live on Qik.com. I&amp;rsquo;ll also be showing an early version of LouderVoice for Business if anyone wants a look.
If you have anything you want to show off and would like a mention here on the blog, just drop me a line.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Next OCC in Rubicon Centre in CIT</title>
      <link>/2008/08/15/next-occ-in-rubicon-centre-in-cit/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2008 14:08:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/08/15/next-occ-in-rubicon-centre-in-cit/</guid>
      <description>Well that was a fantastic event today in the NSC. We easily had more than 30 people between OCC regulars and SohoSolo people and some new faces to both.
Thanks again to CorkBIC for hosting and sponsoring.
The networking seemed to work particularly well and I was thrilled to meet some new faces whose products and services were very impressive.
The next OCC is in two weeks on Aug 29th in the Rubicon back to our usual time of 10am.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Next OpenCoffee in NSC on Friday</title>
      <link>/2008/08/13/next-opencoffee-in-nsc-on-friday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2008 19:54:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/08/13/next-opencoffee-in-nsc-on-friday/</guid>
      <description>The next Cork OCC is on this Friday in the board room of the NSC in Mahon. It is a bit different from our normal get-together for two reasons. The first is that it starts at 9am instead of the usual 10. The second is that it&amp;rsquo;s a joint event with SohoSolo. This means we&amp;rsquo;ll have a bigger group that usual. There won&amp;rsquo;t be a formal demo but we will hear a short intro about SohoSolo and the other services of CorkBIC who have been strong supporters of OpenCoffee since it started.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A note from Saul Klein</title>
      <link>/2008/07/24/a-note-from-saul-klein/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2008 18:04:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/07/24/a-note-from-saul-klein/</guid>
      <description>As many of you probably know, Saul Klein kicked off OpenCoffee in London early last year. Here is an email he sent to a lot of the organisers earlier. Some great stuff with a very nice plug for Ireland.
Wow. There are now over 80 of you all round the world (see [www.opencoffeeclub.org](http://www.opencoffeeclub.org/)) - its pretty amazing how its spread over the last year and we have new locations starting every month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>And the next OpenCoffees are....</title>
      <link>/2008/07/17/and-the-next-opencoffees-are/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2008 19:30:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/07/17/and-the-next-opencoffees-are/</guid>
      <description>The following are the next OCCs in Cork:
 * Tomorrow Friday 18th - Luigi Malones on Emmet Place 10am. No formal demos but as always feel free to whip out a laptop and show us all what you are working on. * Friday August 1st - No OpenCoffee. We tend to have minimal turnout on Bank Holiday weekends * Friday August 15th - Joint OpenCoffee-[SohoSolo](http://www.sohosoloireland.com/) meet-up in the National Software Centre in Mahon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Latest Cork OCC Updates</title>
      <link>/2008/07/11/latest-cork-occ-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2008 12:03:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/07/11/latest-cork-occ-updates/</guid>
      <description>Just a few notes on the latest from Cork OpenCoffee.
 * We&#39;re in today&#39;s Examiner! Half page piece including a picture I took at the Tapasol Demo in the Rubicon Boardroom. * Aileen Cussen wants to thank everyone who donated last Friday. She raised almost â‚¬700 from a total of â‚¬4000. In addition, she got multiple offers of help and expertise for the trip to Uganda including Wifi/internet guidance, laptop configuration, CD burning and local contacts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Videos from Map Enable</title>
      <link>/2008/06/29/videos-from-map-enable/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2008 18:32:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/06/29/videos-from-map-enable/</guid>
      <description>I took a series of videos of Paul Harrington&amp;rsquo;s presentation of Map Enable at the last OCC. Some really informative discussion ensued which would be of interest to any startup. Apologies for the sound quality, I really need to get a mini boom mic for my Nokia N95-8GB.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Farewell dinner for Cork OCC Regular</title>
      <link>/2008/06/13/farewell-dinner-for-cork-occ-regular/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2008 08:51:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/06/13/farewell-dinner-for-cork-occ-regular/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve arranged a dinner for this coming Tuesday night in Cork City (final venue decision imminent). It is to wish fond farewell to OpenCoffee stalwart Tom Raftery who is moving to Spain with his family.
If you would like to attend, please let me know by e-mail to conor AT loudervoice DOT com by Saturday night at the latest. It should be a great night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Latest Cork OpenCoffee Videos</title>
      <link>/2008/05/28/latest-cork-opencoffee-videos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2008 10:03:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/05/28/latest-cork-opencoffee-videos/</guid>
      <description>I forgot to mention that I took some videos of the Tapasol demo at last week&amp;rsquo;s OCC. Here they are:
Tapasol 1:

Tapasol 2:

Tapasol 3:

Room Sweep:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TwitterFone goes live</title>
      <link>/2008/05/07/twitterfone-goes-live/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2008 09:39:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/05/07/twitterfone-goes-live/</guid>
      <description>Our second last OpenCoffee was in Luigi Malone&amp;rsquo;s where Pat Phelan, from Cubic Telecom, demoed TwitterFone to us all. We were all sworn to secrecy until the official launch which happened last night. The response, as we all predicted, has been overwhelming.
Apart from the fact that it&amp;rsquo;s a fabulous service, there are some strong lessons to be learned from the TwitterFone development.
 * Do it, do it, do it do it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tapasol to Demo on May 23rd</title>
      <link>/2008/05/05/tapasol-to-demo-on-may-23rd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2008 14:55:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/05/05/tapasol-to-demo-on-may-23rd/</guid>
      <description>The guys from Tapasol have built some very interesting bare-metal provisioning and deployment software. I remember looking into this area in EMC a few years back and being disappointed by what was out there.
It&amp;rsquo;s great to see a local company doing something in this space, particularly one that came about due to the Motorola closure. The guys also recently won an award in this years Genesis Programme.
On Friday the 23rd they will talk about the challenges of deploying software on Unix servers and give a demonstration of their automated solution to build a Unix server from bare metal with a single command.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Phoebe Bright to Demo To-Do App</title>
      <link>/2008/05/05/phoebe-bright-to-demo-to-do-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2008 14:48:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/05/05/phoebe-bright-to-demo-to-do-app/</guid>
      <description>The next demo slot on May 9th will have Phoebe Bright presenting her To-Do application. I&amp;rsquo;ve seen an earlier incarnation of this in action and I think it is very competitive to what&amp;rsquo;s out there and has some unique features. In Phoebe&amp;rsquo;s own words:
**Another To Do List Application** This has been my pet project for two years, but stimulated by a conversation at Open Coffee a few weeks ago, I am heading off in a new direction with it and I&amp;rsquo;d love to get some feedback.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Next Two Cork OpenCoffees</title>
      <link>/2008/04/30/next-two-cork-opencoffees/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2008 10:06:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/04/30/next-two-cork-opencoffees/</guid>
      <description>The next Cork OpenCoffee is on Friday 9th May in the NSC in Mahon. Map here.
Many thanks to Catherine Wall in it@cork for arranging the boardroom in the NSC and to it@cork themselves for kindly sponsoring the coffee.
We&amp;rsquo;ll be back to the Rubicon again on 23rd May.
If you are interested in demoing your product/idea at either session or giving a shortÂ talk on your area of expertise, please shout.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nice piece on OpenCoffee in Silicon Republic</title>
      <link>/2008/04/18/nice-piece-on-opencoffee-in-silicon-republic/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2008 08:26:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/04/18/nice-piece-on-opencoffee-in-silicon-republic/</guid>
      <description>Marie Boran from Silicon Republic has always taken a strong interest in Irish start-up activity. I remember she was the first to get in contact when Paddy&amp;rsquo;s Valley was announced.
She has written a very nice piece in today&amp;rsquo;s Silicon Republic (not sure if it&amp;rsquo;ll be syndicated to Irish Independent or not) about OpenCoffee in Ireland.
You can follow Marie on Twitter here. They&amp;rsquo;ve also enabled a feed of their stories to Twitter here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cork OpenCoffee tomorrow in Luigi Malone&#39;s</title>
      <link>/2008/04/10/cork-opencoffee-tomorrow-in-luigi-malones/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2008 08:24:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/04/10/cork-opencoffee-tomorrow-in-luigi-malones/</guid>
      <description>Just a quick reminder that OpenCoffee is tomorrow at 10am in Luigi Malone&amp;rsquo;s on Emmet Place.
We&amp;rsquo;ve just heard from Pat Phelan of Cubic Telecom that he&amp;rsquo;ll be doing a demo. Given how busy they have been this week, I&amp;rsquo;ve a feeling this is oneÂ not to miss!
Also, since thisÂ batch of the Genesis programme is coming to a close, it&amp;rsquo;d be great to hear from those who took part in it and hear what they gained from it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenBBQ?</title>
      <link>/2008/04/06/openbbq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2008 10:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/04/06/openbbq/</guid>
      <description>What started as a discussion about having an OpenCoffee in the Midlands the other day quickly turned into a proposal for an OpenBBQ in Terryglass on Lough Derg this summer.
Think business networking, free Wifi, top class BBQ and fun.
Evert has all the details so far. Please drop him a line if you think you might go. He&amp;rsquo;s thinking June/July mid-week. If there is enough interest from Cork OpenCoffee we could consider hiring a mini-bus?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We never got past the introductions!</title>
      <link>/2008/04/03/we-never-got-past-the-introductions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2008 13:09:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/04/03/we-never-got-past-the-introductions/</guid>
      <description>This is my second time to write this post as the first one got deleted accidentally. We had a particularly good OCC meet-up last Friday in the Rubicon with four new faces. The round table introductions caused so many spin-off conversations that we ended up not doing anything else!
A welcome then to:
 * Bob Gee of [Connect Promotions](http://www.connectpro.ie/) who seemed delighted by the response of us all to his business (promotional items or schwag as we geeks call it).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
