<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cork on Cork OpenCoffee</title>
    <link>https://localhost/tags/cork/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cork on Cork OpenCoffee</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2011 02:07:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://localhost/tags/cork/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cork Open Coffee August 19th</title>
      <link>https://localhost/2011/08/16/cork-open-coffee-august-19th/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2011 02:07:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://localhost/2011/08/16/cork-open-coffee-august-19th/</guid>
      <description>This week&amp;rsquo;s Cork Open Coffee is on this Friday at The Rubicon at 10:15am (CIT,Bishopstown,Cork).
There are no presentations or demos lined up this week, just open networking.
Want to talk at Open Coffee?
If you would like to give a talk or show off a new product for some feedback
at an upcoming Cork Open Coffee, please get in touch by emailing corkopencoffee@gmail.com
Talk to you all on Friday Don’t forget to follow @corkopencoffee on Twitter!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>World Class Solutions Sales workshop in Cork</title>
      <link>https://localhost/2009/07/15/world-class-solutions-sales-workshop-in-cork/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2009 13:36:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://localhost/2009/07/15/world-class-solutions-sales-workshop-in-cork/</guid>
      <description>World Class Solutions are holding a workshop in Cork on the 29th July for business owners who want to kick-start their sales.
Participants will learn new sales and marketing techniques. They can also bring their promotional materials and website address and get individual help to improve them.
The workshop will run from 9.30 am to 1.30 pm, Wednesday the 29th of July in the Regus Centre the City Gate in Mahon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slides from The Embedded Entrepreneur</title>
      <link>https://localhost/2009/06/26/slides-from-the-embedded-entrepreneur/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2009 14:13:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://localhost/2009/06/26/slides-from-the-embedded-entrepreneur/</guid>
      <description>This morning Tom Doherty from Beyond Targets spoke to Corks Open Coffee about a concept called The Embedded Entrepreneur.
Toms talk, directed at Entrepreneurs encouraged those aiming to create a business to put their idea to the test as early as possible. Embed a pre-start entrepreneur in a host customers site for a fixed period of time and only launch a start-up once proof of concept has taken place within a host customer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cork Open Coffee March 20th</title>
      <link>https://localhost/2009/03/19/cork-open-coffee-march-20th/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2009 08:53:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://localhost/2009/03/19/cork-open-coffee-march-20th/</guid>
      <description>This weeks Cork Open Coffee will be in Nosh + Coffee, Careys Lane (Just off Patricks Street) in Cork at the usual time of 10am.
There are no presentations this time, we&amp;rsquo;re trying out a new location after Luigi Malones don&amp;rsquo;t seem to like having customers.
Some reviews of Nosh + Coffee:
Nosh+Coffee, Cork
Review of Nosh+Coffee
See you there!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SOHO Solo Conference</title>
      <link>https://localhost/2009/02/13/soho-solo-conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2009 08:37:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://localhost/2009/02/13/soho-solo-conference/</guid>
      <description>Film producer and entrepreneur Lord Puttnam will deliver the keynote address at the SOHO Solo conference called “Reinventing Oneself in these Challenging Times” in Kinsale next Friday, 20th February 2009.
The half-day conference is aimed primarily at small business owners, entrepreneurs and those with a budding business idea. It takes places at the Kinsale Yacht Club between 10am and 2pm and is an absolute bargain to attend at only €25 including lunch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Open Coffee of 2009 in Cork</title>
      <link>https://localhost/2009/01/05/first-open-coffee-of-2009-in-cork/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2009 19:02:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://localhost/2009/01/05/first-open-coffee-of-2009-in-cork/</guid>
      <description>Happy New Year to all, hope you are refreshed, revived and full of vigor and enthusiasm for what 2009 has to offer all of us flegling businesses in the Cork area!
The first OCC of 2009 is on this Friday, the 9th January in the Rubicon Centre in CIT at our usual time of 10am-12pm.
We want to have a brainstorming session for ideas for improvements for the group itself or ideas of events/additions that we can implement in 2009.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
