<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>corkbic on Cork OpenCoffee</title>
    <link>https://localhost/tags/corkbic/</link>
    <description>Recent content in corkbic on Cork OpenCoffee</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2008 15:14:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://localhost/tags/corkbic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cork OCC&#39;s Monday talk and next two events</title>
      <link>https://localhost/2008/10/15/cork-occs-monday-talk-and-next-two-events/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2008 15:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://localhost/2008/10/15/cork-occs-monday-talk-and-next-two-events/</guid>
      <description>Monday&amp;rsquo;s special OCC in the NSC was exactly that, special. The boardroom was jammed full of people, many of them new faces to hear Tom Keane talk about Nitrosell, his history and his advice on growing a business. I was completely riveted by what he had to say since so much of it applied directly to what we are doing in LouderVoice. The questions at the end told me that he had affected many of the attendees in the same way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Special OpenCoffee on Monday 13th (Not Friday!)</title>
      <link>https://localhost/2008/10/07/special-opencoffee-on-monday-13th-not-friday/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2008 13:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://localhost/2008/10/07/special-opencoffee-on-monday-13th-not-friday/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re running a special one-off OpenCoffee this coming Monday (13th) instead of the usual Friday. It&amp;rsquo;s a bit unusual in that we&amp;rsquo;ve invited a speaker to come in and talk about how he grew his business and raised funding. That person is Tom Keane, President of Nitrosell. He has a long history in the software biz and I know I&amp;rsquo;m not the only one who has a ton of questions to ask him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Next OpenCoffee in NSC on Friday</title>
      <link>https://localhost/2008/08/13/next-opencoffee-in-nsc-on-friday/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2008 19:54:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://localhost/2008/08/13/next-opencoffee-in-nsc-on-friday/</guid>
      <description>The next Cork OCC is on this Friday in the board room of the NSC in Mahon. It is a bit different from our normal get-together for two reasons. The first is that it starts at 9am instead of the usual 10. The second is that it&amp;rsquo;s a joint event with SohoSolo. This means we&amp;rsquo;ll have a bigger group that usual. There won&amp;rsquo;t be a formal demo but we will hear a short intro about SohoSolo and the other services of CorkBIC who have been strong supporters of OpenCoffee since it started.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>And the next OpenCoffees are....</title>
      <link>https://localhost/2008/07/17/and-the-next-opencoffees-are/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2008 19:30:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://localhost/2008/07/17/and-the-next-opencoffees-are/</guid>
      <description>The following are the next OCCs in Cork:
 * Tomorrow Friday 18th - Luigi Malones on Emmet Place 10am. No formal demos but as always feel free to whip out a laptop and show us all what you are working on. * Friday August 1st - No OpenCoffee. We tend to have minimal turnout on Bank Holiday weekends * Friday August 15th - Joint OpenCoffee-[SohoSolo](http://www.sohosoloireland.com/) meet-up in the National Software Centre in Mahon.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
