<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>david reilly on Cork OpenCoffee</title>
    <link>https://localhost/tags/david-reilly/</link>
    <description>Recent content in david reilly on Cork OpenCoffee</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 May 2010 13:34:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://localhost/tags/david-reilly/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cork Open Coffee in the Blackrock Castle Observatory</title>
      <link>https://localhost/2010/05/26/cork-open-coffee-in-the-blackrock-castle-observatory/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2010 13:34:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://localhost/2010/05/26/cork-open-coffee-in-the-blackrock-castle-observatory/</guid>
      <description>Thanks to a connection from Damien Mulley , This weeks Cork Open Coffee is taking place on Friday the 28th in the **Blackrock Castle Observatory **in Blackrock in Cork from 10am to 12pm.
For anyone not familiar with the area, here is a link to the Blackrock castle on Google Maps http://short.ie/ bcomap. There is parking around the corner from the castle gates.
Clair McSweeney, Facilities Manager of the Blackrock Castle Observatory has kindly invited us to gather in the The Castle Bar and Trattoria, which is on the right as you enter the castle gates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slides from David Reilly&#39;s talk at Open Coffee</title>
      <link>https://localhost/2009/07/24/slides-from-david-reillys-talk-at-open-coffee/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2009 13:21:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://localhost/2009/07/24/slides-from-david-reillys-talk-at-open-coffee/</guid>
      <description>This morning David Reilly from Reilly &amp;amp; Co Solicitors spoke to Corks Open Coffee about Commercial Law.
It was an excellent presentation, David covered a lot of very relevant topics focused on those in commercial software development in a short time.
Davids presentation was called The Creation, Protection and Exploitation of Software - A Practical and Non-Harming Legal Review and covered the following areas:
 Legal background to ownership of software - VCs and The Exit Strategy Protection and Infringement of software Exploitation of software - how to get it right from the very start  A practical and commercial legal review aimed at software developers and those dealing in IT contracts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cork Open Coffee is on Friday July 24th</title>
      <link>https://localhost/2009/07/22/cork-open-coffee-is-on-friday-july-24th/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2009 11:29:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://localhost/2009/07/22/cork-open-coffee-is-on-friday-july-24th/</guid>
      <description>Hi OCCers,
This weeks Cork Open Coffee is on Friday July 24th in the Rubicon building next to CIT from 10am-12pm.
The Creation, Protection and Exploitation of Software David Reilly from Reilly &amp;amp; Co. Solicitors will be presenting a talk on The Creation, Protection and Exploitation of Software - A Practical and Non-Harming Legal Review.
Topics will include:
  Legal background to ownership of software - VCs and The Exit Strategy</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
