<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>rubicon centre on Cork OpenCoffee</title>
    <link>/tags/rubicon-centre/</link>
    <description>Recent content in rubicon centre on Cork OpenCoffee</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2010 12:55:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/rubicon-centre/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>7 Habits of Effective Websites</title>
      <link>/2010/06/10/7-habits-of-effective-websites/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2010 12:55:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2010/06/10/7-habits-of-effective-websites/</guid>
      <description>This week’s Cork Open Coffee is taking place Friday the 11th of June at 10am in The Rubicon Centre in Bishopstown in Cork (Map).
7 Habits of Effective Websites
Frank Prendergast is a well known and respected Web Designer based in Cork and will give a brief talk on Search Engine Optimisation (SEO) and then open up the topic for further discussion with the group.
Frank has been working in the web industry for over ten years and likes to work with small to medium sized businesses developing or revamping their web presence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Discovery Zone&#39; for new business ideas</title>
      <link>/2010/03/09/discovery-zone-for-new-business-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2010 14:49:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2010/03/09/discovery-zone-for-new-business-ideas/</guid>
      <description>This is an excellent opportunity for brand new business ideas. A new programme called &amp;lsquo;Discovery Zone&amp;rsquo; has been set up in the Rubicon Centre, the host of many Cork Open Coffees.
If you are among the many that aspire to starting your own business but don’t know where to start, then the Discovery Zone could be just the launching pad you need. The programme has been specifically developed to assist experienced professionals, who for a variety of reasons find themselves at a crossroads in their career.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First set of dates for Cork OCC in 2009</title>
      <link>/2009/01/05/first-set-of-dates-for-cork-occ-in-2009/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2009 21:29:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2009/01/05/first-set-of-dates-for-cork-occ-in-2009/</guid>
      <description>Our first OpenCoffee is Friday 9th in the Rubicon Centre in CIT, this gives us the following dates for the next few months. I&amp;rsquo;ll put these on Upcoming.org too so you can add them to your calendar and auto-monitor for changes.
If you&amp;rsquo;d like to host any of the TBD locations or even replace any Luigi one, just let us know on corkopencoffee AT gmail DOT com
 * 09/01: Location = Rubicon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Next two OpenCoffees</title>
      <link>/2008/05/29/next-two-opencoffees/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2008 08:43:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/05/29/next-two-opencoffees/</guid>
      <description>The next Cork OpenCoffee is on Friday June 6th in Luigi Malone&amp;rsquo;s on Emmet Place at 10am. The one after that is back to the Rubicon Centre in CIT.
We won&amp;rsquo;t have a formal demo slot in Luigi&amp;rsquo;s but as always everyone should feel free to whip out their laptops to show us what they are working on.
The Demo Slot on the 20th will have Paul Harrington show us MapEnable.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
