<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>open coffee on Cork OpenCoffee</title>
    <link>/tags/open-coffee/</link>
    <description>Recent content in open coffee on Cork OpenCoffee</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2009 10:19:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/open-coffee/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cork Open Beer</title>
      <link>/2009/08/13/cork-open-beer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2009 10:19:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2009/08/13/cork-open-beer/</guid>
      <description>Cork Open Coffee is going strong each fortnight but there are a few who can&amp;rsquo;t make it on a Friday morning during work hours.
At the last Open Coffee in Nosh+Coffee it was decided to organise an evening event.
Right now the plan is to meet on Friday the 28th of August somewhere in
Cork.
Are you interested in attended an Open Coffee - evening style? Any
recommendations for a location and a time to kick off?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cork Open Coffee March 20th</title>
      <link>/2009/03/19/cork-open-coffee-march-20th/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2009 08:53:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2009/03/19/cork-open-coffee-march-20th/</guid>
      <description>This weeks Cork Open Coffee will be in Nosh + Coffee, Careys Lane (Just off Patricks Street) in Cork at the usual time of 10am.
There are no presentations this time, we&amp;rsquo;re trying out a new location after Luigi Malones don&amp;rsquo;t seem to like having customers.
Some reviews of Nosh + Coffee:
Nosh+Coffee, Cork
Review of Nosh+Coffee
See you there!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minehane Chartered Accountants at Open Coffee this Friday.</title>
      <link>/2009/02/02/minehane-chartered-accountants-at-open-coffee-this-friday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2009 12:19:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2009/02/02/minehane-chartered-accountants-at-open-coffee-this-friday/</guid>
      <description>The next Open Coffee is on this Friday the 6th in the Rubicon at 10am. Michael Minehane from Minehane Chartered Accountants will talk about corporation tax and R&amp;amp;D rules for Irish businesses followed by Q &amp;amp; A.
Book Swap
If anyone would like to swap some business books or recommended reading, please bring them along. I will bring along “The mythical man month” and “Once you&amp;rsquo;re lucky, Twice you&amp;rsquo;re good” if anyone would like to borrow them for a while.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
