<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tom keane on Cork OpenCoffee</title>
    <link>https://localhost/tags/tom-keane/</link>
    <description>Recent content in tom keane on Cork OpenCoffee</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2008 14:07:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://localhost/tags/tom-keane/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Questions for Tom Keane?</title>
      <link>https://localhost/2008/10/17/questions-for-tom-keane/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2008 14:07:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://localhost/2008/10/17/questions-for-tom-keane/</guid>
      <description>As Tom had to fly off the other day, many people didn&amp;rsquo;t get a chance to ask him a question. Head on over to the eWrite Blog and Gordon will pass on any questions you have there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cork OCC&#39;s Monday talk and next two events</title>
      <link>https://localhost/2008/10/15/cork-occs-monday-talk-and-next-two-events/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2008 15:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://localhost/2008/10/15/cork-occs-monday-talk-and-next-two-events/</guid>
      <description>Monday&amp;rsquo;s special OCC in the NSC was exactly that, special. The boardroom was jammed full of people, many of them new faces to hear Tom Keane talk about Nitrosell, his history and his advice on growing a business. I was completely riveted by what he had to say since so much of it applied directly to what we are doing in LouderVoice. The questions at the end told me that he had affected many of the attendees in the same way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Special OpenCoffee on Monday 13th (Not Friday!)</title>
      <link>https://localhost/2008/10/07/special-opencoffee-on-monday-13th-not-friday/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2008 13:16:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://localhost/2008/10/07/special-opencoffee-on-monday-13th-not-friday/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re running a special one-off OpenCoffee this coming Monday (13th) instead of the usual Friday. It&amp;rsquo;s a bit unusual in that we&amp;rsquo;ve invited a speaker to come in and talk about how he grew his business and raised funding. That person is Tom Keane, President of Nitrosell. He has a long history in the software biz and I know I&amp;rsquo;m not the only one who has a ton of questions to ask him.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
