<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cork opencoffee on Cork OpenCoffee</title>
    <link>/tags/cork-opencoffee/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cork opencoffee on Cork OpenCoffee</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2010 08:18:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/cork-opencoffee/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Videos from Your Country Your Call at Cork OpenCoffee</title>
      <link>/2010/04/11/videos-from-your-country-your-call-at-cork-opencoffee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2010 08:18:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2010/04/11/videos-from-your-country-your-call-at-cork-opencoffee/</guid>
      <description>Two videos of the Jump crew in action.
Initial talk to everyone:

Sub-group Brain-Storming:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Next Few OpenCoffees</title>
      <link>/2009/09/26/next-few-opencoffees/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2009 14:31:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2009/09/26/next-few-opencoffees/</guid>
      <description>Here are the upcoming Cork OpenCoffee meetups:
 * Oct 2nd 2009 - Nosh+Coffee, Carey&#39;s Lane * Oct 16th 2009 - Rubicon Centre CIT * Oct 30th 2009 - Nosh+Coffee, Carey&#39;s Lane  Hopefully you can extrapolate further dates and locations from this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photos from last OpenCoffee</title>
      <link>/2009/05/20/photos-from-last-opencoffee/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2009 07:45:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2009/05/20/photos-from-last-opencoffee/</guid>
      <description>Magda Lukasiewicz was at last week&amp;rsquo;s OpenCoffee in Nosh+Coffee and took some great pictures, some of which are below. Check out her site for more brilliant photography.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Should we make Nosh&#43;Coffee our new City Location?</title>
      <link>/2009/03/20/should-we-make-noshcoffee-our-new-city-location/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2009 13:22:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2009/03/20/should-we-make-noshcoffee-our-new-city-location/</guid>
      <description>Should we make Nosh+Coffee our new City Location for Cork OpenCoffee? (surveys)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Today&#39;s OpenCoffee in The Rubicon</title>
      <link>/2008/09/26/todays-opencoffee-in-the-rubicon/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2008 05:15:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/09/26/todays-opencoffee-in-the-rubicon/</guid>
      <description>The next OCC is today in the Rubicon Centre in CIT at our usual time of 10am-12. We&amp;rsquo;ll have one informal demo from a new attendee.
I was also contacted by Brian O&amp;rsquo;Flaherty from UCC who will be there. The directors of the Masters in Business Information Systems (MBIS) programme at UCC are looking to work with Cork companies in the development of products and services for business. For more details see http://afis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Special one-off OpenCoffee in Rubicon this Friday</title>
      <link>/2008/06/29/special-one-off-opencoffee-in-rubicon-this-friday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2008 18:26:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/06/29/special-one-off-opencoffee-in-rubicon-this-friday/</guid>
      <description>The next OCC would normally not be in the Rubicon but we&amp;rsquo;ve decided to have a special joint-one there this coming Friday, July 4th at 10am.
Aileen Cussen, who is an EI D.A. to many of you I&amp;rsquo;m sure (including ourselves) is going to Uganda to help build a school and educate some of the local children for a period of several weeks. It is being done as part of the Lake Lyantonde project which was initiated by the Kabata Farmers Group and run by the local community with an aim of creating awareness of, environmental conservation practices, safe water and sanitation, sustainable agriculture, HIV/Aids, and fostering general development for the community living near Lake Lyantonde.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Next two OpenCoffees</title>
      <link>/2008/05/29/next-two-opencoffees/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2008 08:43:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/05/29/next-two-opencoffees/</guid>
      <description>The next Cork OpenCoffee is on Friday June 6th in Luigi Malone&amp;rsquo;s on Emmet Place at 10am. The one after that is back to the Rubicon Centre in CIT.
We won&amp;rsquo;t have a formal demo slot in Luigi&amp;rsquo;s but as always everyone should feel free to whip out their laptops to show us what they are working on.
The Demo Slot on the 20th will have Paul Harrington show us MapEnable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cork OpenCoffee in The Irish Times</title>
      <link>/2008/04/14/cork-opencoffee-in-the-irish-times/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2008 12:01:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2008/04/14/cork-opencoffee-in-the-irish-times/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m chuffed to see that Haydn Shaughnessy mentions Cork OpenCoffee in his piece in the Innovation Magazine of today&amp;rsquo;s Irish Times. The point of the article is:
If companies want to be innovative in their field, not only do they need to rethink how they do business, but they also have to be willing to step out of their comfort zone He includes two quotes from me on OpenCoffee which I think are true for many of those who attend.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
