<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>mr cotton on Cork OpenCoffee</title>
    <link>/tags/mr-cotton/</link>
    <description>Recent content in mr cotton on Cork OpenCoffee</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2010 10:17:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/mr-cotton/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cork Open Coffee Friday 22nd January</title>
      <link>/2010/01/20/cork-open-coffee-friday-22nd-january/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2010 10:17:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2010/01/20/cork-open-coffee-friday-22nd-january/</guid>
      <description>Cork Open Coffee is back for the new year!
This weeks Open Coffee will be on in the new (and dry) UCC Western Gate building on Western Road. Friday the 22nd at 10am. We will be in Room 231/226 on level 2.
James Little from UCC, a regular at Open Coffee has arranged for a room for us for the morning. Thanks James! Coffee on Friday will be supplied by Mr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cork Open Coffee Friday 11th at 10am</title>
      <link>/2009/12/10/cork-open-coffee-friday-11th-at-10am/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2009 06:33:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2009/12/10/cork-open-coffee-friday-11th-at-10am/</guid>
      <description>This weeks Cork Open Coffee is in the Rubicon Centre, CIT Campus Bishopstown on Friday 11th from 10am - 12pm.This the last Cork Open Coffee of 2009.
There will be 2 demos on Friday. John Dennehy will be talking about his great time tracking application at http://www.assemblypoint.com and Paul Brugger will be talking about a new Twitter application called @Localnumber which allows you to search and instantly receive contact phone numbers for businesses types in your area through Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cork Open Coffee Friday the 13th</title>
      <link>/2009/11/11/cork-open-coffee-friday-the-13th/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2009 19:56:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2009/11/11/cork-open-coffee-friday-the-13th/</guid>
      <description>Hi OCCers,
This weeks Cork Open Coffee is in the Rubicon Centre, CIT Campus Bishopstown on Friday 13th from 10am - 12pm. It will be held downstairs in the lobby area as the Seminar Room is booked.
The demo slot will be taken up by one of our newest regulars, Israel Finnerty. Israel &amp;amp; his partner Dawn Manning will be showcasing their new company FireSale.ie - Ireland&amp;rsquo;s first Buy, Sell, Haggle &amp;amp; Auction website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cork Open Coffee Friday the 16th</title>
      <link>/2009/10/14/cork-open-coffee-friday-the-16th/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2009 10:36:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2009/10/14/cork-open-coffee-friday-the-16th/</guid>
      <description>This weeks Cork Open Coffee is** Friday the 16th at 10am**, in the **Rubicon Centre** in Bishopstown in Cork.
If you havent been to the Rubicon Centre before, take a look at their new site which has some pics and a map http://www.rubiconcentre.ie/
This Week, Joe Scanlon will be demoing a new site that he dreamt up and runs called LittleQuiz. LittleQuiz is a great site allowing you to enter competitions every week to win some pretty great stuff!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Citylocal Cork Sponsoring Cork OpenCoffee</title>
      <link>/2009/09/20/citylocal-cork-sponsoring-cork-opencoffee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2009 08:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2009/09/20/citylocal-cork-sponsoring-cork-opencoffee/</guid>
      <description>Since Cork OpenCoffee began in early 2007, we&amp;rsquo;ve had some intermittent sponsorship of the coffee and scones which has always been appreciated. So we&amp;rsquo;re delighted that Paul Brugger from Citylocal Cork has agreed to sponsor three of the Rubicon sessions (with the first one just two days ago).

This means no more icky instant coffee and the arrival of the great Mr Cotton coffee instead. By the way, well done to Declan for his appearance on TV3 this week.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
